Making history will never be the same again
LOLA is a drama, science fiction, war film directed by Andrew Legge.
Sussex, England, 1938.
Shortly before the outbreak of World War II, Thomasina and Martha Hanbury,
two ingenious sisters, create LOLA, a miraculous machine.
Thomasina Hanbury, played by Emma Appleton.
Martha Hanbury, played by Stefanie Martini.
Lt. Sebastian Holloway, played by Rory Fleck-Byrne.
Major. Henry Cobcroft, played by Aaron Monaghan.
Young Thomasina Hanbury, played by Theodora Brabazon Legge.
Young Martha Hanbury, played by Francesca Brabazon Legge.
Lola is a 2024 American drama film written and directed by Nicola Peltz Beckham, who stars alongside
Raven Goodwin, Richie Merritt, Luke David Blumm, Trevor Long, and Virginia Madsen.
The film, released in the United States on February 9, 2024, was universally
panned by critics and grossed just $648 at the box office.
The film explores themes of sibling relationship, dystopia,
world war ii, time machine, anti-nazi resistance.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and thought_provoking.